Kevin DeLoach

https://github.com/kdeloach

2308 Locust 1F • Philadelphia, PA 19103 • (215)-490-8269 • kdeloach@gmail.com

Summary

Dedicated and professional programmer experienced in working collaboratively as well as independently in order to achieve company objectives.

Technical Skills

Programming: .NET, SQL, PHP, Python, Java, Javascript, Flex, XSLT

Source Control: Git, Perforce, Subversion

Other: Microsoft Visual Studio, Adobe Photoshop, Flash, LATEX

Experience

Elements, Inc. (elementsinc.net), Philadelphia, PA Lead Programmer

September 2008 – December 2011

- Worked with wide range of technologies to meet client needs
- Created project specifications and delivery estimates
- Provided major role in refactoring and developing features for company products
- Coordinated with remote team in a project management role
- Organized product builds and releases regularly
- Established company Wiki to improve team knowledge base

Verve Internet Solutions (boardeffect.com), Philadelphia, PA Web Developer

December 2007 – August 2008

- Website production and technical support
- Maintained and developed content management software
- Worked directly with clients to provide troubleshooting and miscellaneous assistance

Austin District Music Teachers Association

Web Developer (Freelance)

May 2008

• Developed custom web portal to manage events and scheduling

Central High School (centralhigh.net), Philadelphia, PA Technical Assistant

September 2005 – July 2006

- Maintained website and wrote software for managing content
- Worked with faculty to diagnose networking and other issues
- Assisted with computer lab administration, image cloning

Education

Drexel University, Philadelphia, PA

2006

No degree

Central High School, Philadelphia, PA

2002 - 2006